<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Tracker</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_myStuff">My Stuff</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="longText">Over a month after first giving a strong recommendation to the Pixel 2, I can easily still stand by it. In my eyes, it still offers the absolute best overall Android experience, carefully weighing usability and features both in the hardware and software.It's the best Google has made and a fantastic phone I think anyone would be happy using.The screen size is relatively small compared to the rest of the flagship industry, but it offers great one-handed usability with plenty of room to get typical tasks done. The software doesn't have every feature, but it has amazing speed and consistency along with seamless integration of Google's latest features and apps. And then there's the camera. What an amazing selling point. Anyone can pick up a Pixel 2 and take wonderful photos in a wide variety of situations with no photography skills at all.We can all quibble about the value proposition of the larger Pixel 2 XL at $849, with a larger screen and battery not quite justifying the $200 price bump. But when you look at what the Pixel 2 offers for just $649 it's no surprise that I and the rest of the Android Central team rate it so highly. And an extra month of use has only solidified my feelings on this great phone. Even taking its imperfections into account, it's the best phone Google has made and one I think anyone would be happy using.</string>
    <string name="thanksDB">This product uses the TMDb API but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb.</string>
    <string name="thanksMaterial">Thanks to @Eajy and his app "Material Design" for inspiration and reference to Google's Material Design standard.</string>
</resources>
